

CONTACT

Mumbai, India 421204



kjagruti444@gmail.co m

CORE STRENGTH

- Business development
- Strategic planning and review
- Business process mapping
- Expertise in lead generation
- Strong lead development skills
- Converting leads into customers

CERTIFICATIONS

- Sales Strategies and Approaches in a New World of Selling -LinkedIn
- Communicating with Confidence - LinkedIn
- Nano Tips for Peak
 Performance with
 Shadé Zahrai LinkedIn
- Nano Tips to Sharpen Your Critical Thinking with Shadé Zahrai -LinkedIn
- Nano Tips for Developing Magnetic Charisma with Shadé Zahrai - LinkedIn

Jagruti Kadam

I am a highly motivated individual that has been in the Sales and Management field for more than several years, with great passion and commitment. I have managed some of the top business companies in the country and have achieved great success with them. With the experience I gained over the years I have built strong customer base and will continue to do so.

EXPERIENCE

1/2022 - Current

2/2021 - 11/2022

Senior Product Specialist

HUVIAiR Technologies - Bangalore, India

 Identifying potential customers through research and networking activities, then contacting them to set up meetings or presentations

Researching market trends to identify opportunities for new products or services that might appeal to specific clients
Developing and maintaining relationships with clients to increase future business opportunities

- Preparing proposals for new business opportunities or contracts with existing clients
- Communicated issues and updates proactively to accelerate turnaround on client queries
- Analysing complex data regarding consumer patterns and preferences.

Customer Experience Manager LODHA developers - Mumbai, Maharashtra

 Coordinated with various departments (Customer Care, Accounts, Sales Peer Teams etc.) to ensure exceptional customer service and assuring the customers' requirements are met first.

Created a hassle free & seamless experience for the customer with regards to On-boarding, Registration, Loan process, Payments, handing over of the Unit etc. to deliver prompt and accurate service to the customer

Provided payment arrangements, Top up loan, raised exceptions for waiver of delayed charges, providing options within the policies for customer's facing financial difficulty or for retention.

- Met the clients, bankers to resolve issues related to approvals, reconciliation of accounts or other service requests.
- Coordinated for construction status of the respective project with the site team and project departments.

Assistant Manager (Closing)

LODHA developers - Mumbai, Maharashtra

• Increased profitability by developing pipelines utilizing multiple marketing channels and B2B sales strategies.

Increased business with B2B selling and cross selling of commercials and logistic parks

Profiled, targeted and prospected territory within and beyond existing customer base to expand reach and revenue.

Educated customers on available processes and services. Created professional sales presentations to creatively communicate product quality and market comparisons.

10/2018 - 09/2022

- Created strategic sales plans, designed to increase sales, customer loyalty and market awareness.
- Boosted team morale and overall sales volume by creating incentivizing sales contests.
- Monitored sales team performance and provided training to help reach targets.

Sales Executive Mohan Group

 Building and maintaining healthy business relations with high net worth and corporate clients.

Selling and cross selling of products from branch with existing base of customers. Assist with organizing promotional events.

Gather leads from Internet and contact the Clients to understand their requirement.

Managed customer relationships through consultative sales techniques to attain individual sales goals.

Contacted customers to set-up appointments, monitor satisfaction levels and upsell additional offerings.

EDUCATION

2021

Master of Business Administration Marketing Welingkar Institute of Education - Mumbai, MH

2013

Graduate bachelor of commerce University of Mumbai - Mumbai, MH

7014 - 10/2018